MAURICIO **ZAMORA MOYA**

Phone: +506 83705378

Email: mauzamoramoya@gmail.com

Direction: Desamparados, San José, Costa Rica

ABOUT ME

I am a systems engineer with experience in front end development, support and quality control of projects. I have developed applications and websites. I am passionate about technology. Organized, creative, proactive, resilient with the ability to adapt to challenges and develop new skills to improve my professional profile.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SYSTEMS ENGINEERING COSTA RICAN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY | SAN JOSÉ 2018 - 2021

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Typescript

React JS

Next JS

Redux

Bootstrap – styled components SASS

S.O Windows and Linux

PYTON - C# - JAVA

Git - GitHub

SQL Server - My SQL - Firebase

JIRA - Slack

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mauric io-zamora-0279231b5/

https://mauriciozamoram.github.io/ Portfolio/

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB

DECEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Creation of web applications with Intuitive design, strong preference for UX/UI.
 Easy to use and understand.
- Management of JSON and RESTful services.
- Development of unit tests using Jest and react-testing-library to check the behavior of the components and functions of the web application.
- Creation of UX/UI components following the best practices and design patterns.
- Design software solutions to meet customer requirements.
- Use of tools and interface creation processes (Webpack, NPM).
- Support customers on software products.

INTERNSHIP

INFOSGROUP OF COSTA RICA AUGUST 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

- Design intuitive templates with good UX/UI design.
- Implementation of new functionalities.
- Design software solutions to meet project requirements by refactoring existing code and fixing bugs.
- Perform software control and quality tests.
- Create readable documentation.
- Assist in the development of responsive, scalable and maintainable web code.
- Developed ability to complete delegated tasks on time and work in a collaborative development environment.
- Operate infrastructures within ITIL and ITSM methodologies.

CERTIFICATIONS

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN SYSTEMS ENGINEERING DECEMBER 2021

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1k1MGnTPW5lru4AMwBREySmPB64tAL6Tk/view?usp=sharing

MASTER IN JAVASCRIPT FRAMEWORKS

JUNE 2022

 $\frac{\text{https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-9f53dc7e-837a-4eb2-bd73-5950e1ed1a3c.pdf}$

TEAM WORKFLOW WITH GIT

APRIL 2022

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1bHxZY3vm5U-8SfiUPvPnE7ZLGmAFbga1/view?usp=sharing

AZURE FUNDAMENTALS

MAY 2022

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1YXZvZLoZCzqXI fpD6IJd xtM7a-212x/view?usp=sharing

SCRUM FUNDAMENTALS

JULY 2022

https://www.scrumstudy.com/certification/verify?type=SFC&number=925768